export const data = {
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Unturned originally started as a Roblox game.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "FIFA is popular soccer video game published by EA Games",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Luigi is Mario's brother",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "God of War made an appearence in Mortal Kombat Complete",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Counter Strike is not a shooter game",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Books: Science Fiction",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Isaac Asimov wrote Dune",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Books: Science Fiction",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Malachi Constant is a character created by Kurt Vonnegut",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "School: Geography",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Budapest is a European City!",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "School: Geography",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Kathmandu is the world's highest capital!",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "School: Geography",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Bolivia is a country in Africa!",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
  ]
};
